<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Verification Setup on Harness Modernization Workshop</title>
    <link>/030_automated_canary/verification_setup.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Verification Setup on Harness Modernization Workshop</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language><atom:link href="/030_automated_canary/verification_setup/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>7.1 Metrics Server Install</title>
      <link>/030_automated_canary/verification_setup/71_k8s_metrics_server.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/030_automated_canary/verification_setup/71_k8s_metrics_server.html</guid>
      <description> Kubernetes Metrics Server Installing the Metrics Server can be done in one kubectl command.
kubectl apply -f https://github.com/kubernetes-sigs/metrics-server/releases/latest/download/components.yaml </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7.2 Prometheus Installation</title>
      <link>/030_automated_canary/verification_setup/72_prometheus_install.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/030_automated_canary/verification_setup/72_prometheus_install.html</guid>
      <description>Prometheus Installation Harness can facilitate the installation of Prometheus. For this workshop, the Prometheus deployables have been configured to be accessible by the workloads in the EKS Cluster in the Git Repository.
Setup -&amp;gt; AWS Canary Lab -&amp;gt; Services + Add Service
 Name: Install Prometheus Deployment Type: Kubernetes  Once you hit Submit, click on three ellipses on the right hand side to Link Remote Manifests.
Enter the following information:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7.3 Prometheus Deployment</title>
      <link>/030_automated_canary/verification_setup/73_prometheus_deployment.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/030_automated_canary/verification_setup/73_prometheus_deployment.html</guid>
      <description>Prometheus Deployment To deploy something in Harness, defining a Harness Workflow will define the steps on the deployment will be achieved.
Setup-&amp;gt; AWS Canary Lab -&amp;gt; Workflows + Add Workflow
 Name: Deploy Prometheus Workflow Type: Rolling Deployment Environment: The EKS Cluster Service: Install Prometheus Infrastructure Definition: My EKS Cluster  Click Submit and you are ready to deploy.
In the upper right hand corner of the Workflow, click Deploy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7.4 Connecting Prometheus</title>
      <link>/030_automated_canary/verification_setup/74_prometheus_connect.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/030_automated_canary/verification_setup/74_prometheus_connect.html</guid>
      <description>Connecting Harness to Prometheus In order to connect Harness to Prometheus, you need the accessible URL endpoint. To grab the HTTP accessible address, run the following command.
kubectl describe service prometheus-service Copy down the LoadBalancer Ingress address from the output of the kubectl command:
a8241cbf8317f4c1ab5507fbce9d576c-671821569.us-east-2.elb.amazonaws.com
You can navigate to the Prometheus UI to validate installation by adding port 8080 for example: https://a8241cbf8317f4c1ab5507fbce9d576c-671821569.us-east-2.elb.amazonaws.com:8080
Add Prometheus as a Verification Provider To wire Prometheus to Harness, setup as a Verification Provider.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
